<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<company>
  <title>Containcorp</title>
  <based-in>London, UK</based-in>
  <founding-date>2020</founding-date>
  <website>https://containcorpgame.com/</website>
  <press-contact>
    plasmarcstudios@gmail.com
  </press-contact>

  <!-- Google analytics ID: -->
  <analytics></analytics>

  <!-- <phone></phone> -->
  <!-- <address> -->
    <!-- <line> -->
      <!-- Street -->
    <!-- </line>
    <line> -->
      <!-- City -->
    <!-- </line>
    <line> -->
      <!-- Country -->
    <!-- </line> -->
  <!-- </address> -->

  <socials>
    <social>
      <name>Steam</name>
      <link>
        https://store.steampowered.com/app/2483140/Containcorp/
      </link>
    </social>
    <social>
      <name>Discord</name>
      <link>
        https://discord.gg/hjpFzzS
      </link>
    </social>
    <social>
      <name>Youtube</name>
      <link>
        https://www.youtube.com/channel/UC92eNdWwMQ-wrdOPOYgTfUQ
      </link>
    </social>
  </socials>

  <description>
    Containcorp is a story generator and simulation game inspired by the SCP-universe. Players assume the role of a facility director, with the task to manage a top-secret facility that contains and experiments on anomalous entities. Containcorp is set in its own mythos with anomalies being continually added through development.
    
    It takes inspiration from the management aspects of Prison Architect, the story generation of Rimworld, the tone of Lobotomy Corporation, the rich lore of the SCP universe, the deep simulation of Dwarf Fortress and the atmosphere of Severance.
    
    Contain eldritch horrors within the facility. Implement containment procedures to handle dangerous anomalies and restore order from containment breaches. Engage in tactical combat with hostile entities, and hold the defence against raids. Design and construct multi-story buildings or burrow underground utilising a plethora of resources. Create efficient power and pipe networks grids to handle your facility's logistic needs. Manage individual character injuries, desires, and emotions. Conduct scientific experiments to unlock technologies with an extensive research system. Onboard human test-subjects for high-risk experiments. React to dynamic events with a bespoke Storyteller system.
    
    Built for Windows, Containcorp is developed by Plasmarc Studios, and we've been working on it since 2020.
    
  </description>
  <pitch>
    hi
  </pitch>

  <!-- Choose between a single block: -->
  <history></history>

  <!-- Or multiple blocks: -->
  <!--
  <histories>
    <history>
      <header></header>
      <text></text>
    </history>
  </histories>
  -->

  <trailers>
    <trailer>
      <name></name>

      <!-- Pick one: -->
      <youtube>
        <!-- Video ID only, not the full URL -->
      </youtube>
      <vimeo>
        <!-- Video ID only, not the full URL -->
      </vimeo>
    </trailer>
  </trailers>

  <awards>
    <award>
      <description></description>
      <info></info>
    </award>
  </awards>

  <quotes>
    <quote>
      <description></description>
      <name></name>
      <website></website>
      <link></link>
    </quote>
  </quotes>

  <additionals>
    <additional>
      <title></title>
      <description></description>
      <link></link>
    </additional>
  </additionals>

  <credits>
    <credit>
      <person></person>
      <role></role>

      <!-- Optional: -->
      <website></website>
    </credit>
  </credits>

  <contacts>
    <contact>
      <name></name>

      <!-- Pick one: -->
      <mail></mail>
      <link></link>
    </contact>
  </contacts>
</company>
